♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Trinity, in English]
With a jaw-breaking score of 92.7…
And still the reigning queens
of Royale Rumble!
[Velma, in English] I beg to disagree!
There should be no animals
being harmed in the competition!
Eh, what's this?
- [audience] Ohh!
- Whoa!
That's right!
What's the use of having talent
if it won't wake up ever again?
[Trinity] Because the rules were violated…
[in English] we declare that
Karayom Kweens is the winner!
[audience cheering]
[music continues]
- [Atoy] Audrey?
- [audience cheering]
Huh?
[Red] Wait. I'm going
to send you a picture. Okay?
Watch him.
He might try to infiltrate Velora Bay.
[Trinity, in English] If he shows up,
he will be killed on the spot.
[Uno] I can infiltrate that.
[in English]
Just plug this into their computer.
[Mercado, in English] This is very risky.
[in English] They must follow protocol,
even if they're civilians.
[Atoy] I'll take care of them, sir.
[receptionist] Michael V., is that you?
Ah-- oh--
- [Karla] Ouch!
- Who's that? [gasps]
Son of a thread!
Karla, it's dangerous here!
- Eh, why are you allowed to come?
- You.
- [Atoy] I'll guard you.
- [Karla] Me?
- You! You're so stubborn, huh!
- We'll escape from here.
- Huh? Escape?
- [goon speaking indistinctly]
What will you do?
[Ibyang] Brother, bother,
can I go to the bathroom?
I really need to pee.
That's Rizaldo Coloma, right?
[Kurt] He's the corrupt mayor and the--
the bagman!
- [swishes]
- [groans]
[in English] Meet the princess of Amrati.
[Martina, in English] You know, my husband
would've loved to meet you too.
So, you're here too, you animal?
[Atoy] You even joined forces,
you two demons.
♪ Like a bubble, like a bubble ♪
♪ When the cutter ♪
[Samir, in English] Surprised to see me?
Turns out you wronged both me and Samir.
Where are my children?
PREVIOUSLY
[music fades]
[footsteps tapping]
Why are you still looking
for your children?
You won't see them again.
[somber music playing]
Now I'll finish you.
- [thumps]
- [grunts]
[ominous music playing]
You want to get back at me, don't you?
Revenge!
You're only brave because
you have many people with you.
You stay there. No one interfere, ah.
- [grunts]
- [thumps]
[tense music playing]
- [grunting & groaning]
- [thumping]
[theme music playing]
- [motorcycle revving]
- [sewing machine whirring]
- [scratches]
- [snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[thumps & gunshots]
- [music intensifies]
- [clicking]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
[man] Bro, look at this.
Hmm. Looks normal.
But seems like there's something.
[suspicious music playing]
Hey. What are you doing here?
Bro.
[music continues]
Possible.
- [music fades]
- [rousing music playing]
[thumping and thudding]
- [growling, grunting, groaning]
- [rousing music playing]
[in English] Uhm, please excuse me.
I-- I have to go check on something.
Okay, okay.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Did you see the tall man
who was standing here a while ago?
Ah, uhm…
[in English] No, no tall man.
He was…
[security, in English]
Is there any problem, Mr. Ambassador?
[in English] I am looking for Atoy Padua.
I knew it was him!
He owes me plenty!
He will pay!
[security] How does he look like, sir?
[in English] He is a tall man
in a black suit.
Uhm, wait, wait. I have a picture.
Ah, there. This is him.
[tense music playing]
He looks like the bodyguard
of the princess of Amrati.
- Princess of Amrati?
- Yes, sir.
Is she here?
She's-- supposed to be sick!
[music fades]
There! That's her!
[ominous music playing]
[suspicious music playing]
[Martina, in English] This is…
Tonet and her brother.
[What-- what the hell.
Is he here?
[Mongki] From Tabang Lupa.
How did he end up here?
Madame, maybe you're being haunted.
That's the one you killed
at the mall, right?
[heavy music playing]
[in English] You know, you don't have to
remind me of that, Mongki, huh.
[Martina] Let's go.
You're ruining the night.
You animals.
Especially you, Martina.
[music swells]
- [music fades]
- [tense music playing]
[grunting & groaning]
[thumping]
[suspicious music playing]
[goon] Stay there! Eat there too!
- [music continues]
- [door closes]
- What?
- Why?
I'm hungry. And I even saved some for you.
I got salt and pepper too, eh.
That has sleeping pills in it.
Huh? Are you sure?
- Yes. Sleeping pills.
- Sleeping pills?
Oh, no. I already took a bite.
[ominous music playing]
Drink water. Lots of water, huh.
All of it? So it won't be too effective.
They want us to fall sleep,
so they can transfer us to the ship.
- [tense music playing]
- [gasps softly]
To the ship?
To the ship.
Huh? Where will they take us?
I don't know.
[music fades]
Eh, what about them?
[rousing music playing]
[Kalaf, in English] Thank you all
for coming to my birthday.
The drinks and food are plenty.
- [in English] Where's Atoy?
- [Karla] Huh?
He left. Why?
Someone saw him here.
We're dead. Let's go, let's leave.
Wait, wait. Don't you have a performance?
If we leave now, they'll notice, right?
Of course they'll look for you.
Let's just follow the plan.
Let's wait for Uno.
[suspicious music playing]
Karla, we need to go to them.
They need to know what's happening.
[Kalaf, in English] Ah, before we continue
with the party…
and with the other performers,
I would like to call
my, uhm, special guest.
The princess of Amrati.
Princess Priya Noorani! Where is she?
[tense music playing]
Thank you for coming to my party,
Princess Priya.
I'm glad you are feeling better.
[music swells]
[in English] Of course, she is better.
[in English] She is not princess.
[intense music playing]
Sir Padua, I'm in.
- [panting]
- [soft rock music playing]
Where are you now?
[Mercado, in English] All you have to do
is plug this into their computer.
Once you do that,
our IT team can access their system.
- [computer blipping]
- [music swells]
Hey! Who are you?
[staff 1]
What are you doing here? Security!
- [action music playing]
- [grunts]
- [thudding]
- [groaning]
- [thumping]
- [grunting & groaning]
[computer blipping]
- [thumping]
- [grunting & groaning]
- [thumps]
- [grunts and groans]
Huh.
[thumps, then thuds]
- [grunts & groans]
- [music continues]
[grunts and groans]
[groaning]
[music fades]
Oh, my god!
- [in English] You are an impostor!
- [Karla] No--
You are not princess!
[Kalaf, in English]
I don't believe this! Who are you?
[suspicious music playing]
Who are you?
You are with Atoy.
Where is he?
Uh, I don't know! Please, let me go!
[in English]
You are not going anywhere!
Help me!
- [gun cocks]
- [women squeal]
[shouts] Let her go!
- [gunshots]
- [screaming and panicking]
[chandelier shattering]
Let me go!
- Karla, let's go!
- Let me go!
- Let's go!
- Gavin?
- Karla, come on!
[screaming and panicking]
[gunshot]
- [Kurt] Go. Go, go, go!
- Hide! Cover, cover, cover!
- [gun cocks]
- Get this.
We're ready, we're ready.
- [grunts and groans]
- [gunshots]
Brother Kurt,
Atoy didn't teach us that, ah.
[in English] I served in the marines.
And it's a secret!
We need to move! There are more of them.
[Kurt] Let's go!
[gunshots]
[music continues]
[computer blips]
[soft rock music playing]
Yes!
[in English] Sir Mercado,
the package is loaded.
Radar systems are disabled.
Security is breached.
[Mercado, in English] We have control.
Rescue and back up operative
are now engaged to move to Velora Bay.
Copy, sir.
[grunts]
[music continues]
Where are my children?
[grunting]
[rock music playing]
[grunts]
[gunshots]
[gunshot and thumps]
[tense music playing]
[Mongki] Martina!
Martina!
[tense music playing]
Martina.
Mongki, I've been looking for you.
[in English] What the hell is going on?
[panting] I spoke with Boss Red.
He said Atoy is here.
Looks like he's the one
shooting it out in there.
[in English] Oh, so what are we
supposed to do now?
Where is he?
He said he'll follow.
But he said you should go ahead
to the port.
We'll go back for Boss.
[in English] Okay, fine. Go!
- Go, go, go, go, go, now!
- Come on. Come on, come on.
[tense dramatic music]
- [slaps]
- [gasping]
[in English] How dare you!
How dare you your face! [gasping]
It was you-- you killed my sister.
[gasps]
You killed my sister. I'll kill you!
[Emerson gasps]
[music swells]
[grunts]
- I'll kill you!
- [grunts]
I'll kill you!
You killed my sister! [grunts]
[in English] Tonet is a nosy girl!
She deserved to die!
And there's nothing you can do about it!
- [Emerson] That's what you think!
- [groans]
Let me go.
- I'll kill you!
- Let me go.
- Let me go!
- You killed my sister!
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- Let me go.
- [Gavin] Brother Emerson, don't!
[Emerson grunting]
- [Gavin] Brother!
- [Emerson] Let me go!
Gavin! She killed Tonet! You killed Tonet!
You killed my sister!
[growls]
Hey! Go ahead! Try it!
What are you waiting for?
- [Mongki] Try it!
- Shoot her!
Hurry!
- Martina, let's go!
- [grunting]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[in English] Gavin,
what are you doing here?
Helping fight the bad people.
- [gasping]
- Is it true you killed Tonet, huh?
- [Karla] Gavin, she--
- Is it true?
[in English] No matter what I've done,
I'm still your mother!
No!
- You should be on our side, Gavin!
- No, Mom!
- What are you saying?
- You need to pay for that!
[gasps] No. No, what are you saying?
Come home, come home!
Just come home with us, please.
Mom, no!
Stop this! Stop this, Gavin! Stop this!
Did you do it, Mom?
It doesn't matter!
You should be on my side!
[shouts] No! You need to pay for that!
[grunting]
[Martina] Why are you doing this?
- Mom…
- [thumps & gunshot]
Is it true?
- [Martina] Why are you doing this?
- It doesn't make sense!
[tense music playing]
- No!
- Mom, stop!
- Gavin, you need--
- Let go of that!
Get out of the way! Please, son! Please!
- Stop it! Get out of the way, son.
- Drop that!
- Mom!
- Get out of the way!
- I'm telling you--
- No!
- Let go, Mom!
- Get out of the way!
Gavin, please! Gavin, let go! Let go!
- Let go--
- [gunshot]
[gasps]
- Gavin?
- Oh, my god.
Gavin! Gavin, Gavin!
Oh, my god. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it. I swear, Gavin. Please.
- Wake up, baby. Baby!
- [Karla] Gavin, Gavin!
I'm so sorry. Please!
- Gavin?
- [sobbing] No!
Look what you've done!
Gavin! My son, please wake up!
- Wake up, Gavin.
- Wake up, Gavin! Please!
- Please don't do this.
- Gavin.
- No one move!
- [gunshot]
- [Uno] No one move!
- [Martina] Wake up.
- [others] Hey. Hey, hey!
- [Uno] Stop!
[Uno] Gavin! What's happening to you?
- Gavin!
- Gavin.
Ah, hold Mommy!
- [Martina] What's happening?
- Hold Mommy!
- [shouts] What?
- What are you doing?
Surrender now with Mongki, Mom!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
There's someone here,
there's someone here! [gasps]
- [gunshots]
- Gavin!
- [screaming and panicking]
Martina! Martina! Let's go!
- Let me go!
- No! Wait!
[Nestor] Come on!
Come on, come on, come on! Come on!
[gunshots]
[ominous music playing]
[speaking in Russian] Say hi to God.
[gunshots]
[intense music playing]
- Huh?
- Janine?
- Oh?
- Don't sleep.
- We still have a plan!
- I'm sleepy-- it's making me drowsy.
Then just slap me, okay. [grunts]
Just slap me.
[slaps]
No effect. Oh, no.
Or maybe…
[music continues]
Janine, I know how to wake you up.
- Bite the side of your nail.
- This one?
[Ibyang] Bite it.
Then pull the skin.
[gasps] Quick, quick! Hurry!
[clicks tongue, grunts]
Oh, there.
Ouch! [groans]
- What was that?
- [sneaky music playing]
[shushing]
- Sorry.
- [groans]
Okay. Lie down, lie down.
Close your eyes, but don't sleep, okay.
I really won't be able to sleep.
It stings, eh.
Go, close your eyes.
[music fades]
Take that one.
[suspicious music playing]
Boss, we'll load this onto the ship.
No, Atoy is there.
We'll take them somewhere else.
[phone rings]
Hello? Oh? Where are you?
[music fades]
[footsteps clomping]
No, no, no. Wait.
Go ahead. [grunts]
[ominous music playing]
Atoy is here.
I'm sure he's got company.
What?
Gavin is here?
Hello? Hello? What happened?
- [groans]
- [tense music playing]
- [goon] Boss!
- [groans]
[groans]
Janine, Janine! Hurry!
- Hurry, Janine!
- [groans]
- Go after them!
- Okay, Boss!
[Uno] Gavin! Hurry!
Wait. I need to find Martina.
She shouldn't be able escape.
Where's Atoy? Maybe he needs our help.
Okay. Let's find Atoy, and the children.
That's our priority.
Come on.
Karla, stay here with Gavin.
Come on, come on!
I'm fine, just a graze!
[rousing music playing]
Let's go.
[suspicious music playing]
Come on.
Hurry.
Why did you stop? Come on!
They might catch us!
Go ahead. Go to your father.
Huh? We'll both go to Tatoy.
[Janine] No, no.
They'll just catch us.
Just run.
What about you?
I'll create a distraction,
so they won't follow you.
Come on! Here, this way!
Hey! Where are you going?
[tense music playing]
Where's the chopper?
[crickets chirping in the distance]
[dagger swishes]
- [dagger swooshes]
- [guttural cry of pain]
[tense music playing]
You think you can escape, you corrupt man?
- [dagger swooshes]
- [guttural cry of pain]
You're a plague to Filipino taxpayers!
[Rizaldo] Ouch! [guttural cry of pain]
[Ibyang] Tatoy!
- [Ibyang] Let me go!
- [sobbing]
You're truly bad, you bald man!
[heavy music playing]
- Tatoy!
- [Atoy] Child?
- My child.
- [music swells]
Ibyang!
- [electronic blipping]
- [intense music playing]
[officer, in English]
You are all under arrest!
[in English] I have diplomatic immunity!
- [Janine] Mommy.
- [theme music playing]
[in English] Thank God you're okay, child.
Janine, where is Ibyang?
Let my child go.
Face me.
You're really a skilled tracker,
Master Cutter.
But you've cornered me now.
So, we all go down together.
Tatoy!
UP NEXT
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias